(Leonard:)Thank you, Dr. Cooper.
(Sheldon:)You're welcome, Dr. Hofstadter.
Okay, I'm gonna go
get your discharge papers.
[SHELDON CLICKS TONGUE]
(Penny:)What?
(Sheldon:)You seem like
a perfectly pleasant person.
I can't understand why women
have such a hard time loving you.
(Leonard:)Can you open this for me?
- Can I see your stitches?
- Sure.
[RETCHING]
(Raj:)Answering the question once and for all
why Wolowitz bailed out of medical school.
(Penny(entering):)Leonard, congratulations.
- What for?
- Your Facebook status update.
"Leonard Hofstadter is in a relationship."
(Leonard:)What? No. No, that's not right.
(Howard:)Oh, man, did you switch your status
before she did?
(Howard:)Speaking as an expert,
way to look needy.